{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "City forest National Park",
        "explanation": "City forest",
        "correctAnswer": "Jammu & Kashmir"
      },
      {
        "question": "Dachigam National Park",
        "explanation": "Dachigam",
        "correctAnswer": "Jammu & Kashmir"
      },
      {
        "question": "Kistwar National Park",
        "explanation": "Kistwar",
        "correctAnswer": "Jammu & Kashmir"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hemis National Park",
        "explanation": "Hemis",
        "correctAnswer": "Ladakh"
      },
      {
        "question": "Great Himalayan National Park",
        "correctAnswer": "Himachal Pradesh"
      },
      {
        "question": "Nanda Devi National Park",
        "explanation": "Nanda Devi",
        "correctAnswer": "Uttarakhand"
      },
      {
        "question": "Gundy National Park",
        "explanation": "Gundy",
        "correctAnswer": "Tamil Nadu"
      },
      {
        "question": "Eravikulam National Park",
        "explanation": "Eravikulam",
        "correctAnswer": "Kerala"
      },
      {
        "question": "Keibul Lamjao National Park",
        "explanation": "Keibul",
        "correctAnswer": "Manipur"
      },
      {
        "question": "Nameri National Park",
        "explanation": "Nameri",
        "correctAnswer": "Assam"
      }
    ],
    "states": ["Jammu & Kashmir", "Himachal Pradesh", "Tamil Nadu", "Kerala", "Assam", "Maharashtra", "Karnataka", "Ladakh", "Uttarakhand", "Manipur"]
  }
  